<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Blockheads</title>
    <description>The Blockheads - Exploration, mining, crafting and building sandbox game</description>
    <link>https://theblockheads.net/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://theblockheads.net/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 11:48:02 +1200</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 11:48:02 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Blockheads 1.7 Out Now!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the biggest update ever! With pets, animal breeding, expert mode, skin customization, pizza ovens, new mobs, rainbow cake, a new D-Pad option for control, free HD textures, gem blocks, wind effects and HD clouds, yak shaving, shark riding, and SO MUCH MORE!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As well as the large number of big new features there have been many, many little tweaks and fixes to help you get the most from your experience while playing The Blockheads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t forget to give expert mode a go, for a new challenging progression which makes it a whole new game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +1300</pubDate>
        <link>https://theblockheads.net/2018/03/15/1.7-out-now.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://theblockheads.net/2018/03/15/1.7-out-now.html</guid>
        
        <category>blockheads</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Blockheads 1.7 Launches March 15th</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Finally! After a long wait, it is my pleasure to announce that The Blockheads 1.7 - THE BIGGEST UPDATE EVER - will be out on the 15th of March, just over a week from now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are many new features, and a huge number of improvements and bug fixes in this update. 1.7 brings pets, animal breeding, expert mode, skin customization, pizza ovens, new mobs, a new D-Pad option for control, free HD textures, shark riding, and much more!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To reduce the number of empty server worlds, help us to cover our hosting costs, and make for a better multiplayer experience, 1.7 also will require In App Purchase for creating and topping up all cloud hosted worlds. So now is your chance to top up your server worlds with Time Crystals while you still can. More details on the reasoning behind this change can be found here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://forums.theblockheads.net/t/a-change-to-server-credit-in-1-7/55577&quot;&gt;A change to server credit in 1.7&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further details on all of the exciting new features will be announced just before 1.7 goes live. See you next week!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +1300</pubDate>
        <link>https://theblockheads.net/2018/03/07/1.7-launches-march-15.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://theblockheads.net/2018/03/07/1.7-launches-march-15.html</guid>
        
        <category>blockheads</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Blockheads 1.7 coming soon!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;With the upcoming release of 1.7, it’s time for a fresh new front page, which you can see at &lt;a href=&quot;http://theblockheads.net&quot;&gt;http://theblockheads.net&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1.7 is in the final stages of testing, and will be released within the next few weeks. It’s been a really long wait, I know! But this is the biggest update since the game was first launched, so it’s taken a long time to get all of the bugs ironed out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for your patience, not long now!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +1300</pubDate>
        <link>https://theblockheads.net/2018/02/11/welcome-to-the-new-blockheads.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://theblockheads.net/2018/02/11/welcome-to-the-new-blockheads.html</guid>
        
        <category>blockheads</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
